Hello and welcome back to On the Brink.
I'm Nick Carter.
Today we're sitting down with Paolo Arduino,
the CEO of Tether.
This is actually his second episode on the show.
I'd forgotten we interviewed him before.
That was in June, 2020, almost five years ago.
That episode was called Managing the Growth of Tether.
At that time, the supply of Tether was about $9 billion.
Today it's $143 billion.
I think they've managed the growth okay.
Obviously such a pleasure to have Paolo on the show.
He doesn't do that many public appearances.
We cover a lot of terrain in this episode.
Paolo has visited the US recently.
He's coming on to share his views on the stablecoin bills
making their way through Congress.
And we discuss whether they wanna eventually come unsure
in the US.
It was also reported today
that Tether is pursuing a big four audit.
We talk about that and why they were unable to do that
in the past.
We talk about their move to El Salvador
and Tether's desire to be more public-facing,
showcasing some of the data and the usage of the,
what they estimate is 400 million global users
of the stablecoin.
This is a great wide range of conversation.
I'm really glad Paolo came on.
Let's dive right into it.
["Dance of the Sugar Plum Fairy"]
Today we have very special guest Paolo Arduino
from Tether.
Very, very excited.
Obviously, timely conversation.
Lots of news items around Tether breaking,
including today, the announcement
that you guys are pursuing a big four audit.
Paolo, thanks so much for joining us.
Thank you for having me, Nick.
It's a big pleasure.
So there's so much to talk about.
I don't even know where to start.
Yesterday, Trump spoke at the Digital Asset Summit,
or I don't know, DAS in New York,
and he said, quote,
dollar-backed stablecoins will help expand the dominance
of the dollar for many years to come.
It'll be at the top and that's where we wanna keep it.
It also came out yesterday,
you tweeted Tether was the seventh largest sovereign buyer
of UST bills in 2024 with 33 billion of purchases.
How are you feeling generally about where Tether is today
in the political environment in DC?
All right, there is a lot to unpack there.
So I want to point out yesterday,
I think my tweet was too short,
but if you take the image that they posted yesterday
and you look at the first three,
the top three were Cayman, Luxembourg,
and then you had UK, I think, fifth or sixth.
But Cayman and Luxembourg, they host a lot of hedge funds.
So when you see those numbers,
you actually need to discount the fragmentation
of the different hedge funds.
So I believe that actually,
if you were looking at real numbers,
Tether would be top three buyer of US Treasuries in 2024.
And on the rear end, you could see China and Japan
for different reasons they have been selling US Treasuries.
Japan, of course, needs to,
they need to support their national currency
that is not doing very, very well.
And China, I think there is a clear interest
in de-dollarization in the world
and selling T-bills potentially is being used as a weapon,
like a financial weapon.
They have still, I think,
770 billion dollars to go in US Treasuries.
So I think, you know, I,
when also went in DC recently,
I made of this point a very important part of my discussion.
I believe that there is gonna be,
and I'm pretty proud because I created this term.
Everyone knows about the deep seek moment
for artificial intelligence.
That was a clear, I think it's beautiful
to use that analogy because we saw how Trump announced
500 billion dollars in investment
in artificial intelligence infrastructure one day.
And then very next day, China came out with the deep seek.
And so clearly they didn't develop,
they didn't finish the V1 the next day very, very,
I think would be very timely,
but I think that they had in the pocket
that they decided to announce it in this very specific moment.
So what I think is going to happen is potentially
is a deep seek moment for the US dollar gemini.
And that I think is what we should be prepared for.
And so when Tether builds and build for the last 10 years,
the biggest distribution network for the US dollar,
physical distribution network and digital distribution network,
we can enter in the details later about that.
But so when we did that we, and why we are doing it,
when we are in Africa, when we're in central South America,
in these places, in most of the time there is Tether
and then there is China, right?
So China is building highways, schools, hospitals, stadiums.
There is no US presence in Africa.
There is no almost US presence in central South America.
There is a lot of China.
And so there is definitely, I think the will
from the BRICS countries to build infrastructure,
to physically infrastructure,
and then eventually launch an attack to the US dollar
and more heavy attack to the US dollar
to de-dollarize the world.
And I think that is going to be, it will happen.
First, the BRICS countries trying to create
a digital currency backed by a bunch of national currencies.
I think that quickly realized that it was not possible
because they don't trust each other
with their national currencies.
But then what they realized that many people would like
a digital currency backed by gold.
So if you see the gold price today
and what happened in the last and the clear information
that everyone has of China and India
and other national banks buying a lot of gold,
I think that they are preparing for that.
And then they're preparing for a gold backed stable coin
but run by BRICS.
And let me know if I'm saying the quiet part aloud,
but I think it's very, I think will happen by 2025 or 2026.
So when I'm in DC and I'm explaining
what we are doing is better and why we are,
the fact that we have 400 million people using our product
and in fact, they're using US dollar,
we're buying back the T-bills and all that.
Then the, I basically what I'm also saying is like,
is that it's not easy for us, right?
So we are a simple company
or a building this distribution network.
And to us, the importance of the stable coin bill
is not simply about just making a regulation
on a new technology is in my opinion,
a matter of national security
and that's how it should be treated.
And there is a huge difference between
and the other part of that explain is
that there is a huge difference about rightfully so,
lawmakers in the US are looking at stable coins
as something that should be used domestically, right?
They are mainly, their first interest
is regulating stable coins on the US soil
because that for customer protection and all that,
that is completely fine.
But is, I think it's not correct to think
that the same product that works in the US
where you have a high competition
through all the possible payments means
that will work outside the US in Africa
and Central South America and so on.
So there has to be a concept of a foreign stable coin
that operates mostly internationally
that can sure can be accessed
on the secondary markets everywhere,
but does not issue to US people
because it's focusing on all the emerging markets
and also a very, a domestic stable coin
that focuses on the US market
because that is mostly institutional
and based and focused
and also will focus on servicing
or competing with the PayPal and Zelle
and cash up of the world, right?
So that is the message that I'm trying to give
and explain I think in general works,
is working because people understand the importance
now of stable coins.
Without the data points that we have,
it's very hard to understand the importance
of stable coins, not only USDT,
but USDT is the biggest one out there
in the emerging markets to fight in the streets, right?
So we never talk to any institution outside the US.
We don't go to institutions in Brazil.
We don't go to institutions in Central Asia,
but we go in the streets, right?
We build our adoption from the ground up.
We knock door by door almost.
That's how we build these crazy, crazy numbers.
Paolo, we haven't seen you in the US much before.
I mean, I think it's a clear sign
that you're showing up to Washington to make your case.
Are you happy with what you've seen
from the bills that are making their way through Congress
and we have the House and the Senate,
they're a little bit different, they're changing.
Are you generally happy with what you're seeing
or what you wanna see from this legislation,
assuming it passes?
So I think the Senate bill is quite interesting.
I think it captures the importance of stable coins
that operate internationally that they are very much anyway
under US scrutiny and will remain under US scrutiny
because they would need, based on this bill,
to abide to US law enforcement requests and regulations.
So that, I think, is very important.
We follow US laws and regulations
when it comes to freezing.
We work, I think we are the only stable coin,
including the US stable coins,
that onboarded the FBI, US secret services.
We work with the DOJ almost daily and the Treasury.
So, and on the other side,
allows for domestic stable coins
that are thought to basically
focus on the US markets.
And it makes sense on the House bill
that is still, I think, a draft discussion.
I'm a little bit less familiar,
but I think that the Senate bill is moving fast
and has, I think, is very well thought.
And now, I believe the parent company is based on the BVI
and I know that you obviously have affiliations worldwide,
Switzerland, El Salvador,
I wanna talk about that in a second.
Is it your intent or desire to one day
have some operations in the US
or even ultimately onshore the business into the US?
That's a very good question.
So, I think that Tether International,
the international stable coin should remain international
just because it makes, you know,
that's not, is not suited to be a competitor to PayPal,
for example.
But definitely given, and we are going to watch the bill
for the requirements for US domestic stable coins.
And we would be open to create a domestic stable coin
in the US because we still have,
I believe that we have the best technology also for the US,
but would be clearly a different business model.
And so, we would need to do a bit of research
and understand how we can play in the US.
That is a market that we never played into.
And, but that is very exciting.
It sounds very exciting.
But nevertheless, both the international stable coin
and the domestic stable coin would go through a full audit.
That's why we hired the new CFO that you mentioned.
Simon has incredible experience.
He went through multiple contentious full audits.
I say, I mean, the Tether one should not be contentious.
I mean, our balance sheet is very easy.
Nevertheless, when you have Senator Warren
and Operation Choke Point 2.0,
and big four auditors are discouraged
to take on the crypto customers, that's not easy.
I would call that contentious.
So now I think we are in a good place.
I think that the audit will remain
and is top of our priority list.
But now with the change of administration in the US,
that change demonstrated and signaled
to the big four auditing firms,
that is okay to work with the crypto firms.
And so we are already seeing that change
with much more openness towards us.
Yeah, this is, I'm really glad you brought this up.
So first of all, I mean, I'm not gonna speak too soon,
but congrats.
I mean, I think a lot of people have been waiting
for the big four to be willing to engage with you.
And no one talks about the fact
that there is this political campaign
against the audit firms via the audit regulators in the US.
Warren had a campaign against the PCAOB and the AICPA
to get them to dissuade the audit firms
from dealing with crypto firms.
So this is like the audit version of choke point.
So like choke point was bank regulators and banks.
This is audit regulators and auditors.
And I think people don't understand
this is one of the reasons why it was hard to get an audit.
The politicians in Washington
didn't want the audit firms deal with crypto firms.
So you're saying you've noticed a real shift in attitude
since the new admin?
Yeah, and by the way,
thank you for everything that you have been doing
to highlight operation choke point 2.0,
because definitely that was a well thought attack
to the entire industry, right?
As you said, it was not just for the banks
and the correspondent banks,
but was an entire attack to also from multiple angles.
So it was very hard to come back for companies
that are like nation companies in a nation industry,
like the crypto industry.
So yeah, I think we are seeing a change.
We are seeing a shift
because also most of the big four audit firms,
the leading team is in the US, right?
So if you have an administration in the US
that tells you, well, you should not deal with crypto,
then it's very hard to change their minds.
But something is moving and I'm very pleased to see that.
Yeah, I'm very excited as well.
Now, in terms of El Salvador,
I mean, you made a very interesting announcement recently.
I think you said you'd be moving the headquarters there.
You will have some base of operations there.
Can you say more about that and how that even came to be?
Yeah, El Salvador is a great place.
First of all, it's a beautiful country
run by a president and the government
that demonstrated their ability to push change
and make the country probably now one of the best countries
in South Central and South America for living
is definitely the safest country in Central
and South America.
While it was actually is the safest country in the Americas
while it was the murder capital of the world.
So on top of that, they have been supporting Bitcoin
really early on since 2021.
We went through all the process there
and helped with Bitcoin support,
but also they are the first country that started support
and understand very well digital assets in general
and broader.
And also they created the digital asset law
that is very thorough, but well thought.
And also they added recently, well, one year and a half ago,
they added a stable coin law.
By the way, they are the first country
creating a very thorough and sensible stable coin law.
It's much better than Mika.
I've been very vocal against Mika
just because I believe that it's going to create
the systemic risks in European banks.
Because if Mika for a big stable coin like Tether
would force 60% of reserves in an insured cash deposit,
I think it's a very bad idea.
We saw what happened with a competitor
that had some money in Silicon Valley Bank
that was in an insured cash deposit.
Imagine having 60% of that.
So it's not, and one of the things that I'm telling to
and I'm trying to advocate for
is to have a stronger requirements
when it comes to US treasuries or any way in Europe.
One requirement could have been
the top four economies and by government bonds
from those top four economies.
That would have made sense,
but actually keeping 60% in an insured cash deposit
is a very bad idea.
And on top of that, now they want to,
a couple of days ago, I saw the press release
about their interest in doing the digital euro.
Sorry if I'm sidetracking here,
but clearly Europe is, in that press release,
they said that the digital euro for them
is a way to prevent foreign stable coins,
foreign currency stable coins
to eat up the market for euro.
And my opinion, the euro as a currency is dying
and not because of the, because of USDT is dying
because in Europe doing business is almost impossible.
And the GDP of Europe was cut in half
compared to 20 years ago compared to the US economy.
So long story short, El Salvador is the first country
that has a sensible stable coin legislation.
All the other places, either you have Europe,
that as I said, I ranted five minutes about it,
or you have sandboxes in other places,
but sandbox is not helpful for that are given the size.
And now your engagement with El Salvador,
is this just your sort of physically domiciling
some operations there, like how deep does that go?
Will you be employing locals as part of Tether?
Will you be changing your registration?
What does that look like?
Yeah, definitely we are hiring people there.
We have our headquarters, we are renting out an office,
but we are building a tower.
I think it's, to us makes sense.
Like some people ask me, oh, why not the US, right?
But again, we work in emerging markets,
developing countries.
So we need, El Salvador for us is the door
to central and South America.
We base, so when we designed the working model of USDT,
we designed based on the personal,
the family stories of our employees.
So we have people coming from 70 different countries now,
well, 60 different countries.
And we, everyone of these people have different problems
with, they saw different problems in their countries
with their families.
So that is exactly how we designed USDT.
So for us, it does not make any sense to be in Wall Street.
We should be in the trenches with our own people.
So you mentioned 400 million Tether users.
I was looking on chain, I don't know where,
I think I might've heard you say that
on a different show as well.
I looked on chain yesterday,
I could find around a hundred million addresses.
I know an address is not a person, of course,
and people have accounts at exchanges.
And so it's not a one-to-one mapping,
but is this a study that you've done?
Like, how are you, can you give us a sense
of where you're getting this data from?
Yes, I think we had our chief economist
that was, Philip Gradwell was at Chainalysis first.
Now it came to us, a published few, couple months ago,
published the first analysis
on how we calculate the number of users.
So there is a very high activity on blockchains
across all the different blockchains and bridges.
And of course we also count addresses that receive some USDT
and then they keep it for 24 hours and they send it.
So not every single address has to have USDT all the time,
but they need to have USDT most of the time, right?
Or at least a certain number of times per month.
Plus we have good contacts with many exchanges,
centralized exchanges.
Unfortunately, non-custodial holding of crypto
is still not very popular.
I believe that we should work hard to improve that.
Just for multiple reasons, right?
The matter of reduced trust on exchanges,
a bit more responsibility.
But most of the reason why people don't do that
is because UX sucks.
So we want to try to change that.
We might be able to prove it,
prove this change in the next year or so.
We are going to launch few products around this concept.
But going back there, still what we are seeing,
there is enormous amount of people that use USDT
only on exchanges.
They don't want to hear what is a blockchain.
They don't care what is a blockchain.
If they want just to use peer-to-peer trading
on Binance and some other exchanges,
they want just to, if you are in Buenos Aires,
if you want just to, you have Binance Pay or Bitfinex Pay,
you accept the payment, it goes to your account
and you pay another person in Bitfinex or Binance
through that in your ecosystem, through the account.
There is no blockchain transaction, all that.
But when we query the different centralized exchanges,
we get incredible numbers out of,
in terms of user base of Tether.
So it's a mix of, there is a lot of,
I would calculate a lot of on-chain activity,
but also there is a huge amount of USDT,
primarily it's almost entirely
all the different cryptocurrency exchanges.
Plus you have to sum all the different smaller exchanges
that are like very local, like the Turkish one,
the Argentinian ones and all that, right?
So we try to collect all the information from many.
And we discount that, actually we discount the number a lot
because we assume that there is a lot of some overlapping
between different exchanges.
That's very interesting, thank you.
And Philip is an amazing guy
and did great work at Chainalysis.
So it's a great hire you've made.
Do you plan on diving deeper into the data
to understand geographic segmentation of users
or usage modes by typology?
I mean, I get asked this all the time.
It aren't stable coins just for trading,
like what's the real world usage?
Do you plan on diving into this kind of data?
That is exactly what Philip is going to do.
He is building, he put together a massive data warehouse.
It's in progress still, right?
So, but he's building an incredible data warehouse.
I was talking to a few people,
very high profile people in the last couple of weeks.
We showed just the first version of the dashboard
that we have at Tether to understand
how it's being used and all that.
They never seen anything like that.
And again, it's just the beginning.
It's a fairly expensive endeavor,
but I think we'll pay off
because there is not super precise information, of course,
because blockchain is not perfect for that.
But you can derive the more,
now we are connecting Chainalysis
and probably other 15 different vendors,
and we are building our own heuristics.
And the level of details that we're going to get,
now already is almost insane,
but the level of details that we're going to get
in the next six to nine months
is going to be out of our minds.
Yeah, I mean, as a stable coin nerd and a data nerd,
I couldn't be more excited.
So whenever you're ready, please Sunday my way.
I love that, I love that.
I'm getting very excited just listening to you.
I want to talk about the balance sheet investments.
So, Tether's made a lot of very interesting investments,
not just in crypto, obviously you hold a lot of Bitcoin,
but AI, brain computer interfaces, Rumble,
the video company, agricultural companies.
I think it was reported Uventus, the soccer team.
Is there a common thread in terms
of the balance sheet investments Tether's making
or is there just a purely financial approach
or how do you think about that?
So, when we say balance sheet,
I want to clarify that is outside the reserves,
all the investments in these companies.
So, we have a different allocation.
So we made around 20 something billion dollars
in the last couple of years, two, three years.
So, there is a different approach between,
we have different categories.
So, there is the more long-term strategic investment,
very low yield return,
but very strong is adequate agriculture investment.
The company has a lot of land.
So, I believe that is very strategic.
And almost like stable coins and land, gold, Bitcoin,
to me are part of the same story.
We have stable coins, we have gold, we have Bitcoin.
You have to live somewhere,
like land is going to be quite important.
I believe it's something that will be important forever.
So, that is a particular category, I would say.
Gold and Bitcoin, we are gold bugs and Bitcoin bugs.
So, clear, we started, we accrued,
I think around 50 tons of gold over the last,
well, especially between 2020, 2022,
was very good buy, good average price.
So, yes.
So, before every single BRICS country started to buy.
So, now they are pushing our bags of gold.
These investments in private companies
and other commodities,
is there a strategic rationale with Tether
or is it just you want to diversify,
you don't just hold cash?
There is.
So, I talk about almost everything
that is mostly either long-term
or it has been pure investment and hedge,
but everything else, for example, Rambo,
I think Rambo is set to become
one of the most important companies in the US economy
when it comes to social media and streaming.
So, they're very bullish on Rambo
and plus Rambo is set to,
Chris Pavlovsky is big supporter of Bitcoin.
They add the Bitcoin to their balance sheet.
And so, just imagine if they had more than 70 million users
and they have basically almost the entire wealthy America
as subscriber to Rambo.
So, imagine, so Rambo sold around 853 million dollars
worth of gold between 2023 and 2024.
Imagine what a Rambo wallet could be with Bitcoin inside.
So, and stable coins inside.
So, to me, Rambo is perfectly set to become,
to bridge a clear Web2 company
to a more modern approach to create an ecosystem
that provides services that are social media services,
but also add as part of the ecosystem,
also the concept of money.
So, I'm very bullish on that.
Also part of the balance sheet,
when it comes to, for example, Northern Data,
artificial intelligence investment
is one of our biggest investments.
The opportunity there is just massive.
It's very profitable.
We entered the game before that than almost anyone else.
So, it's already a very profitable business.
And on top of that, Tether is building,
has a very strong AI team.
We count around 60 people now.
And we are building our own models
and we are building our own,
own inference, peer-to-peer inference platform.
So, I'm very excited about that specifically.
Then, most of the rest of the investments
we invest in more than 90 portfolio companies
is actually to build,
to build the biggest distribution network for US dollar.
So, actually most of our effort is exactly that.
So, a few days ago, I posted,
a couple of weeks ago, I posted about our approach
to Africa where we build kiosks with solar panels on top.
And there are batteries inside with,
rechargeable batteries, 140 watt per battery.
And we sell subscriptions to the service
for three USDT per month.
For three USDT per month, you get four battery swaps.
We have more than 300 or almost 500 kiosks now.
We are scaling up to 10,000 kiosks in Africa
now that we prove the concept in the next year and a half.
We have already, with the 34, 500 kiosks,
we have already hundreds of thousands of customers.
And we perform more than 10 million swaps, I believe,
in the last, just in the last year.
So, the concept is great because first of all,
in Africa, you have 600 million people
that don't have energy at home,
but still they have flip phones or cheap smartphones.
They have a small TV maybe and a few things like that.
And of course, light bulbs and things like that, right?
And fridge.
So, these batteries can actually power
some small machinery with 140 volts.
So, it's very cool because it is a change
if we are successful.
And our plan is in five years to have around 200,000
of these kiosks, if we can scale very well.
So, first of all, it's a change that you can see from space
because you can light a continent.
If you ever saw Africa from space, it's very, very dark.
And on top of that, all this economy will run on USDT.
So, we believe that we can bring on,
only in Africa, 50, 60 million new USDT users
and create one of the biggest economies
around the US dollar in Africa.
So, that is very unique as an approach,
but that is one company.
We have another 89 to go that are doing other things,
but with a similar ethos and philosophy,
like how we can, either there are digital businesses
or there are physical businesses
like bodegas in Central South America.
We have a network of hundreds of thousands of bodegas
that are all dealing with USDT.
That is one of the reasons why it's not easy
to displace USDT in central, in emerging markets,
just because it's not, I don't mean to be rude,
but it's not a Silicon Valley game.
This is like game of being in the trenches
and building like, every day you wake up
and you gain one meter in the street
and you get people adoption.
So, while in the last 20 years
with the concept of globalization,
most of the investors were pushing companies
that had the physical distribution networks,
were pushing these companies
to sell the physical distribution network and rent it back
because it was a center of cost.
What we have been doing was the complete opposite.
We started buying physical distribution networks
to ensure our presence on every single territory.
Do you worry about, I mean, you're going from zero users
to 400 million in under a decade.
Do you worry about being too successful
about crypto-dollarization in some of these countries
and in emerging markets and being blamed for inflation
and the local currency, things like that?
I think Millet is a very, well, had some problems recently
but was on a very right track before that.
And he understands very well that the problem,
the success of the US dollar
is not because of the success of the US dollar.
I mean, if the Argentina phase of was perfect,
people would not use the US dollar in Argentina.
So, if you don't fix the country,
sure, you can blame everyone.
It's easy to blame everyone else for your faults,
but clearly, if there is a problem in the local economy,
if, and, you know, what usually is happening
is that the independent from the US dollar,
what central banks do in the emerging markets
is they print their own currency
and use it to buy back dollars on the public markets
to defend the effects rate.
But, you know, they are trying to do the same.
They're just basically trying to defend an effect
that is impossible to defend.
The beauty in finance is that financial markets
are, cannot be drugged.
If you try to change the rules or you try to, you know,
inflate or move something in a forced way,
in a direction, it's physics.
Financial markets are purely driven by physics.
So, you cannot game them.
You cannot trick them.
Eventually, they will go in the direction
that will be always a natural force
to go in the right direction,
where they were supposed to go in the first place.
So, point being is that until you fix the economy,
you can blame everyone,
but, you know, you have first to fix the economy.
So, obviously, it's well reported
you guys have a relationship with Canter, Fitzgerald.
They manage a lot of your treasuries.
Obviously, Howard Lutnick is now the Commerce Secretary.
Has anything changed with your relationship with them
since he came into office?
Is he more hands off now
or do you still have a good relationship with the guy?
We don't have any more direct relationships with Howard
because now he's in office
and also has more important things to do.
And on the other side,
we have still great relationship with Canter
and we still keep the vast, vast, vast majority
of our treasuries in Canter, Fitzgerald.
We need, given the size of Tether,
we need the primary dealer.
We need someone that also offers overnight reverse repos
and a very liquid repo book
and access to the, basically, direct access to the Fed.
That is super important to us
and so we're very grateful for the relationship.
Also, because they looked at Tether
and they took their time to do their due diligence on Tether
even during Operation Shock Point 2.0.
So we are very respectful and grateful to the people
that helped us when the entire former administration
wanted to kill our industry.
Last question, I think, for now.
On business model stablecoins,
there is this new sector of interest bearing
and I know the legislation in the US,
pending legislation, has some language around
not permitting interest bearing stablecoins
so maybe it won't be relevant here.
But we offshore, there's this notion of paying interest.
Tether, of course, does not pay interest.
To its users, it's still grown very, very well
in recent years.
Do you feel any disruption
in the core stablecoin business model
from the emergence of interest bearing stables?
I don't for multiple reasons.
First of all, okay, let me change my answer.
For the US market, I think it will be tricky
because in the US,
people now are under all the biggest stablecoins
in the US market are paying interest.
They can call it in a different way,
but oh, they are paying interest.
Now, the main disruption could happen to them.
Now, it's quite interesting because what will happen
if they have to stop paying the interest?
So where their market cap will go,
that will be a very interesting question.
Outside the US, if you go in Argentina,
where their intraday volatility of their Argentina peso
is more than 4% probably, or at least on a weekly basis,
definitely more than 4%,
if you give them 4% per year, it's not very exciting.
They just want to know that they have a dollar.
For them, they transition from having to buy cash bills
in the streets to have the same thing
but on a smartphone.
So they're very happy without having the interest.
Of course, if you talk to a rich Argentinian
that can buy T bills, that is a different thing.
But most of our user base in the emerging markets
is unbanked.
So for them, having a safe dollar
is the most important thing in the world.
So giving 4% more is not very interesting to them.
So I don't think our business wallet will be impacted.
I think that many, probably others,
will see their business in model impacted
if the regulators will really look at what they're doing.
And I think we welcome competition.
We think that although outside the US,
competition will be very hard almost for everyone,
for anyone, because if you don't go in the streets
as we do, there is no way to grow.
And that's what we did and it's very hard to do.
So we welcome people, more people coming,
more competitors coming to Africa.
But yeah, we'll be very exciting.
Well, Paolo, I think we're gonna leave it there.
Any last word from you?
Any myths you wanna bust or tether
is obviously a very unfairly maligned company.
Any last word from you?
I met you the first time we were in Oslo,
I think for the Oslo Freedom Forum in Paris, I'm gonna say.
And look, many things changed.
I remember very well the conversation at dinner.
I think it was very helpful.
I mean, I started doing that like before that event,
but I think the Oslo Freedom Forum
was the second public event that was doing, right?
So I had to learn a lot myself.
We went through hell and back as a company.
So, and I think I'm seeing what makes also,
I'm being very public, but was never in the US.
I see the difference that makes me be in the US.
So I will be in the US much, much more frequently.
Well, we're glad to have you.
Paolo, this has been great.
Best of luck with everything.
Thank you.
Thank you very much, Nikita, for having me again.